Guide to the William David Allred Papers 1969-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Political File, 1966-1980
  - Texas Building & Construction Trades Council (Box 83)
  - Texas Chest Foundation (Box 83)
  - Texas Child Care '76 (Box 83)
  - Texas Civil Liberties Union (Box 83)
  - Texas Coalition for Utility Regulation (Box 83)
  - Texas Costal & Marine Council (Box 83)
  - Texas College of Osteopathic Medicine (Box 83)
  - Texas Commission for the Arts & Humanities (Box 83)
  - Texas Commission for the Deaf (Box 83)
  - Texas Commission on Jail Standards (Box 83)
  - Texas Commission on the Status of Women (Box 83)
  - Texas Committee for the Humanities (Box 83)
  - The Texas Commodore (Box 83)
  - Texas Congress of Parents and Teachers (Box 83)
  - Texas Conservation Council, Inc. (Box 83)
  - Texas Conservation Union (Box 83)
  - Texas Conservative Union (Box 83)
  - Texas Conservative Victory Fund (Box 83)
  - Texas Consumers Association (1975) (Box 83)
  - Texas Consumer Finance Association (Box 83)
  - Texas Cooperative Ginners Association (Box 83)
  - Texas Council of Administrators of Special Education (Box 83)
  - Texas Council for Exceptional Children (Box 83)
  - Texas County & District Retirement System (Box 83)
  - Texas County Judges' & Commisioners' Association (Box 83)
  - Texas Credit Union League & Affiliates (Box 83)
  - Texas Criminal Defence Lawyers Association (Box 83)
  - Texas Daily Newspaper Association (Box 83)
  - Texas Deepwater Port Authority (Box 83)
  - Texas Democratic Study Caucus (Box 83)
  - Texas Dental Association (Box 83)
  - Texas Dental Hygienists Association (Box 83)
  - Texas Department Community Affair (Box 83)
  - Texas Department of Corrections (Box 83)
  - Texas Department of Health Resources (Box 83)
  - Texas Eastern University (Box 83)
  - Texas Education Agency (Box 83)
  - Texas Electric Cooperatives, Inc. (Box 83)
  - Texas Electric Service Company File 1 (Box 83)
  - Texas Electric Service Company File 2 (Box 83)
  - Texas Employment Commission (Box 84)
  - Texas Energy Advisory Council (Box 84)
  - Texas Enviromental Coalition (Box 84)
  - Texas Farm Workers' Union (Box 84)
  - Texas Fathers for Equal Rights (Box 84)
  - Texas Federation of Cooperatives (Box 84)
  - Texas Finance Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Fine Arts Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Forest Service (Box 84)
  - Texas Forestry Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Forts Trail (Box 84)
  - Texas Good Neighbor Commission (Box 84)
  - Texas Good Roads/Transportation Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Government Newsletter (Box 84)
  - Texas Health Facilities Commission (Box 84)
  - Texas Hearing Aid Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Historical Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Historical Foundation (Box 84)
  - Texas History (Box 84)
  - Texas Horseracing Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Independent Automobile Dealers Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Independent Bird Hunters Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Independent Property & Realty Owners' Organization (Box 84)
  - Texas Industrial Development Council (Box 84)
  - Texas Industrial Vocational Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Institute of Building Design (Box 84)
  - Texas International Airlines (Box 84)
  - Texas Judicial Council (Box 84)
  - Texas LP-Gas Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Landowners Rights Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Land Title Associaiton (Box 84)
  - Texas League of Conservation Voters (Box 84)
  - Texas Library Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Licensed Child Care Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Lutheran College (Box 84)
  - Texas Manufactured Housing Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Mortgage Bankers Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Motor Transportation Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Municipal Power Agency (Box 84)
  - Texas Notary Public Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Ophthamological Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Opportunity (Box 84)
  - Texas Optometric Association, Inc. (Box 84)
  - Texas Optometry Board (Box 84)
  - Texas Osteopathic Medical Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Panhandle Heritage Foundation, Inc. (Box 84)
  - Texas Pawn Brokers Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Personnel & Guidance Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Pest Control Association, Inc. (Box 84)
  - Texas Pharmaceutical Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Podiatry Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Police Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Press Women (Box 84)
  - Texas Professional Educators (Box 84)
  - Texas Professional Fire Fighters (Box 84)
  - Texas Psychological Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Psychotherapy Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Public/Community Junior College Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Public Interest Research Group (Box 84)
  - Texas Recreation & Park Society (Box 84)
  - Texas Recreational Vehicle Association. (Box 84)
  - Texas Register (Box 84)
  - Texas Rehabilitation Commission (Box 84)
  - Texas Retail Grocers Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Retail Merchants Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Retailers Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Safety Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Savings & Loan League (Box 84)
  - Texas School Administrators Council (Box 84)
  - Texas Seafood Distributors Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Shrimp Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Society for Autistic Citizens (Box 84)
  - Texas Society for Medical Technology (Box 84)
  - Texas Society of Certified Public Accountants (Box 84)
  - Texas Solar Energy Society (Box 84)
  - Texas Southern University (Box 84)
  - Texas Southwestern Cattle Raisers Association (Box 84)
  - Texas-Southwest Independent Business Association (Box 84)
  - Texas Seed Trade Association (Box 84)
  - Texas State Arts Committee (Box 84)
  - Texas State Board of Medical Examiners (Box 84)
  - Texas State Board of Examiners of Psychologists (Box 84)
  - Texas State Employees Retirement System (Box 84)
  - Texas State Foster Parents Association, Inc. (Box 84)
  - Texas State Guard (Box 84)
  - Texas State Library (Box 84)
  - Texas State Optical (Box 84)
  - Texas State Railroad (Box 84)
  - Texas Legislative Service - House Daily Report (Box 85)
  - Texas Senate Committee Substitute House Bill 558 (Box 85)
  - General Appropriations Bill 1980-1981 (Box 85)
  - Legislative Clipping Service (Box 85)
  - Texas State Teachers Association (Box 86)
  - Texas State Technical Institute (Box 86)
  - Texas Student Association (Box 86)
  - Texas Student Lobby (Box 86)
  - Texas Surplus Property Agency (Box 86)
  - Texas Technical Society (Box 86)
  - Texas Tech University (Box 86)
  - Texas Telephone Association (Box 86)
  - Texas Thouroughbred Breeders Association (Box 86)
  - Texas Tourist Council (Box 86)
  - Texas Tourist Development Agency (Box 86)
  - Texas Traffic Safety Association (Box 86)
  - Texas Trial Lawyers Association (Box 86)
  - Texas united Community Services (Box 86)
  - Texas Vocational Technical Association (Box 86)
  - Texas Warrant Company (Box 86)
  - Texas Water Conditioning Association (Box 86)
  - Texas Weslayen College (Box 86)
  - Texas Water Development Board (Box 86)
  - Texas Water Quality Board (Box 86)
  - Texas Women's Political Caucus (Box 86)
  - Texas Women's University (Box 86)
  - Texas Women's University Medical School (Box 86)
  - Texas Workmen's Compensation Assigned Risk Pool (Box 86)
  - Texas Young Americans for Freedom (Box 86)
  - Texas Young Lawyers Association (Box 86)
  - Texas Youth Council (Box 86)
  - Texcolor, inc. (Box 86)
  - Texoma Government & Industrial Employees Credit Union (Box 86)
  - Texoma React, Inc. (Box 86)
  - Thacker, William M. Jr. (Box 86)
  - Thacker, William R. (Box 86)
  - Thames, Mr. Leo (Box 86)
  - The Big Thicket (Box 86)
  - The Living Bank (Box 86)
  - Thierfelder, Mrs. Katy (Box 86)
  - Thigpen, Mrs. Nadine E. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Miss Anita Jenell (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Judge Bob L. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Charles (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Mr. & Mrs. D. H. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Doc & Don (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Mrs. Doris (Box 86)
  - Thomas, H. L. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Mr. & Mrs. Jack C. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Jim (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Otis Sr. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Mrs. Reba S. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Ms. W. J. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, W. S. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Ms. Wilma J. (Box 86)
  - Thomas, Mrs. Kenneth (Box 86)
  - Thomesen, Mike (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Angus (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Ms. Betty (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Bob (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Ms. Daisy A. (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Gary (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Ms. Irene (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Mrs. Larry (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Mary L. (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Mrs. Mildred (Box 86)
  - Thompson, Rep. Senfronia (Box 86)
  - Thornton, Dr. Floyd (Box 86)
  - Thornton, Bonnie (Box 86)
  - Thornton, R. E. (Box 86)
  - Thro, Mrs. Edwyna S. (Box 86)
  - Tidwell, Stanley (Box 86)
  - Tigua Indians (Box 86)
  - Tiller, Barney C. (Box 86)
  - Timberlin, D. J. (Box 86)
  - Timms, Stella (Box 86)
  - Tinney, Mrs. B. F. (Box 86)
  - Tipps, Judge. Arthur (Box 86)
  - Titus, Virginia (Box 86)
  - TIPRO (Box 86)
  - Tobacco (Box 86)
  - Todd, Delbert W. (Box 86)
  - Todd, Edgar (Box 86)
  - Todd, Ms. Phoebe (Box 86)
  - Toler, Mrs. Merle (Box 86)
  - Toll Free Numbers (Box 86)
  - Tompkins, Clayton A. (Box 86)
  - Tomlinson, Dr. Jack R. (Box 86)
  - Tony, James (Box 86)
  - Torgerson, Mr. & Mrs. Harris (Box 86)
  - Torres, Reuben (Box 86)
  - Torres, Ms. Suzanne L. (Box 86)
  - Tort Claims (Box 86)
  - Toth, Andrew (Box 86)
  - Toth, Larry (Box 86)
  - Tourism (Box 86)
  - Tourist Development Agency (Box 86)
  - Tower, John (Box 86)
  - Towles, Susan E. (Box 86)
  - Towles, Ms. W. B. (Box 86)
  - Townsend, Mrs. Dianne T. (Box 86)
  - Townsend, George S. (Box 86)
  - Townsend, Terry (Box 86)
  - Townsley, James Howard (Box 86)
  - Tracey, Mrs. Donna (Box 86)
  - Traeger, Sen. & Mrs. John (Box 86)
  - Traffic Safety (Box 86)
  - Trailers (Box 86)
  - Trailways, Inc. (Box 86)
  - Trammell, Ms. Helen R. (Box 86)
  - Transportation (Box 86)
  - Travelers Protective Association (Box 86)
  - Travis, Bruce (Box 86)
  - Travis County (Box 86)
  - Travis State School (Box 86)
  - Treasurer (Box 86)
  - Treat, Ms. Nan (Box 86)
  - Trent, Ms. Linda G. (Box 86)
  - Trial Lawyers (Box 86)
  - Trinity River (Box 86)
  - Trinity University (Box 86)
  - Triplett, Mary F. (Box 86)
  - Trippe, Mrs. Eva (Box 86)
  - Tri-Region Health Systems Agency (Box 86)
  - Trosky, Mrs. C. J. (Box 86)
  - Trousdale, Ms. Leona (Box 86)
  - Truan, Rep. Carlos F. (Box 86)
  - Trucking (Box 86)
  - Truitt, Bob (Box 86)
  - Truitt, Johnny Bernard (Box 86)
  - Truly, H. G. Jr. (Box 86)
  - Truly, Mr. & Mrs. Skip (Box 86)
  - Tschappat, Carol (Box 86)
  - Tucker, Mr. D. W. (Box 86)
  - Tucker, Earl A. (Box 86)
  - Tucker, Mrs. Essie F. (Box 86)
  - Tucker, Mr. & Mrs. Jack A. (Box 86)
  - Tucker, Mr. & Mrs. John R. (Box 86)
  - Tucker, Tommy (Box 86)
  - Tufares, Deno (Box 86)
  - Tuition (Box 86)
  - Tuition Equalization (Box 86)
  - Tullis, Howard L. (Box 86)
  - Tunks, Bert H. (Box 86)
  - Turnbull, Mr. & Mrs. Donald (Box 86)
  - Turner, Mr. & Mrs. A. H. (Box 86)
  - Turner, Mr. & Mrs. B. L. (Box 86)
  - Turner, Ms. Erna (Box 86)
  - Turner, John Alan (Box 86)
  - Turner, Ms. Rhonda (Box 86)
  - Turner, Ms. Anna L. (Box 86)
  - Turney, Ms. Georgia (Box 86)
  - Tuttle, Floyd (Box 86)
  - Twitty, A. R. (Box 86)
  - Tyler State College (Box 86)
  - Tyler, Texas (Box 86)
  - Tyler, Winston (Box 86)
  - U.S. Park Police (Box 86)
  - University State Bank Fort Worth, TX (Box 86)
  - Uselton, Maydell (Box 86)
  - Utility Regulations (Box 86)
  - Utilities (Box 86)
  - Uvalde, Texas (Box 86)
  - Ulery, Ms. Susan (Box 87)
  - Umbarger, Miss Lena (Box 87)
  - Underwood, Mrs. F. J. (Box 87)
  - Underwood, M. J. (Box 87)
  - Underwood, R. L. (Box 87)
  - Underwood, Miss Rene (Box 87)
  - Underwood, Mrs. Tommie (Box 87)
  - Unemployment Agencies (Box 87)
  - Unfair Sales Act (Box 87)
  - Uninsured Motorists (Box 87)
  - Union Carbide Corporation (Box 87)
  - United Churchmen of Greater Wichita Falls (Box 87)
  - United Church Women (Box 87)
  - United Electric Company (Box 87)
  - United Farm Workers Union (Box 87)
  - United Fund of Greater Wichita Falls Inc. (Box 87)
  - United Labor Legislative Committee (Box 87)
  - United Methodist Church (Box 87)
  - United Political Organization (Box 87)
  - United Press International (Box 87)
  - United States Capitol Historical Society (Box 87)
  - United States Fish & Wildlife Service (Box 87)
  - U.S. Public Health Service (Box 87)
  - University Christian Church (Box 87)
  - University of Houston (Box 87)
  - University Interscholastic League (Box 87)
  - University Kiwanis Club (Box 87)
  - University of Texas at Arlington (Box 87)
  - University of Texas at Austin (Box 87)
  - University of Texas at Dallas (Box 87)
  - University of Texas at El Paso (Box 87)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center (Box 87)
  - University of Texas Medical School of San Antonio (Box 87)
  - University of Texas - Permian Basin (Box 87)
  - University of Texas at San Antonio (Box 87)
  - University of Texas System (Box 87)
  - Upper Pease Soil & Water Conservation District (Box 87)
  - Upton, Mr. Robert L. (Box 87)
  - Urban Affairs (Box 87)
  - Urban Renewal (Box 87)
  - Urias, Ed (Box 87)
  - Uriniak, Michael (Box 87)
  - Ulrich, Richard L. (Box 87)
  - Uncapher, Stan (Box 87)
  - Underwood, Miss Barbara (Box 87)
  - Underwood, Dr. Walter L. (Box 87)
  - Unions (Box 87)
  - Union Shop (Box 87)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, & Agricultural Implement Workers of America (Box 87)
  - United Nations (Box 87)
  - United Transport Workers Union (Box 87)
  - U. S. Veterans, inc. (Box 87)
  - University Methodist Church (Box 87)
  - University of Texas (Box 87)
  - Valley Farm Workers Strike (Box 87)
  - Uberig, Mr. & Mrs. Chris A. (Box 87)
  - Udall, Morris K. (Box 87)
  - Uher, D. R. "Tom" (Box 87)
  - Umphrey, Charles Glen (Box 87)
  - Underground Grammarian (Box 87)
  - Underwood, Donald W. (Box 87)
  - Underwood, R. Clay (Box 87)
  - Underwood, Tim (Box 87)
  - Unemployment (Box 87)
  - Unemployment Compensation (Box 87)
  - Unemployment Insurance (Box 87)
  - United Auto Workers (Box 87)
  - United Business & Industry (Box 87)
  - United Community Services (Box 87)
  - United Daughters of the Confederacy (Box 87)
  - United Negro College Fund (Box 87)
  - United Parcel Service (Box 87)
  - United Transportation Union (Box 87)
  - United Way (Box 87)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at Dallas (Box 87)
  - University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston (Box 87)
  - University System of South Texas (Box 87)
  - University of Texas at Tyler (Box 87)
  - Unruh, Mr. & Mrs. Russell J. (Box 87)
  - United States Government (Box 87)
  - Untermeyer, Chase (Box 87)
  - Updegrove, Mr. & Mrs. Dewey (Box 87)
  - Updike, Mrs. J. Allen (Box 87)
  - Urban Transportation Advisory Committee (Box 87)
  - USS Texas (Box 87)
  - Usury (Box 87)
  - Utility Commission (Box 87)
  - Village Glen House (Box 88)
  - Vocational Homemaking Teachers Association of Texas (Box 88)
  - Vogel, Judge Irvin J. (Box 88)
  - Vocational-Technical Training (Box 88)
  - Vocational-Technical Education (Box 88)
  - Vollman, Mr. & Mrs. Chris H. (Box 88)
  - Volunteer Policemen & Firemen (Box 88)
  - Volunteer Policemen & Firemen File 2 (Box 88)
  - Von Dohlen, Tim (Box 88)
  - Von Schlichten, Grace (Box 88)
  - Voting File 1
  - Voting File 2 (Box 88)
  - Vowell, Mr. & Mrs. Raymond (Box 88)
  - Vymer, Roy Don (Box 88)
  - Van Houten, Mrs. E. F. (Box 88)
  - Van Loh, Mr. & Mrs. V. H. (Box 88)
  - Vann, Mrs. W. C. (Box 88)
  - Van Pelt, Ben (Box 88)
  - Vasquez, Mr. & Mrs. Roger (Box 88)
  - Vasquez, I. Fred (Box 88)
  - Vaclacik, John Jr. (Box 88)
  - Vaden, E. E. (Box 88)
  - Vale, R. L. "Bob" (Box 88)
  - Vance, Ms. Doris (Box 88)
  - Vance, Lois (Box 88)
  - VanLoh, Harold (Box 88)
  - Vaughan, Mr. & Mrs. Edward (Box 88)
  - Vaughn, Rev. J. C. (Box 88)
  - Vazquez, Benito (Box 88)
  - Vega, Texas (Box 88)
  - Vehle, Otto M. (Box 88)
  - Vecchio, James S. (Box 88)
  - Veitenheimer, Mr. & Mrs. Leon (Box 88)
  - Velazquez, Rev. Henoch (Box 88)
  - Vending Machines (Box 88)
  - Veneral Disease (Box 88)
  - Verble, Sedelta (Box 88)
  - Vernon Regional Junior College (Box 88)
  - Verett, Mrs. Eddie (Box 88)
  - Vestal, W. D. (Box 88)
  - Veterans (Box 88)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 88)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars (Box 88)
  - Veterans Land Program (Box 88)
  - Veterans Land Board (Box 88)
  - Veterans of World War I (Box 88)
  - Veterinarians (Box 88)
  - Vicars, Harold D. (Box 88)
  - Vick, Rep. Larry (Box 88)
  - Vickery, Glenn (Box 88)
  - Victoria, Texas (Box 88)
  - Vieth, Mr. & Mrs. A. P. (Box 88)
  - Vincent, Mr. Bill (Box 88)
  - Vines, Mr. & Mrs. Donald C. (Box 88)
  - Vinson, Jerry (Box 88)
  - Vissing, Virginia (Box 88)
  - Visually Handicapped (Box 88)
  - Vo. Ag. Teachers Association of Texas (Box 88)
  - Vocational Agriculture (Box 88)
  - Valley View Independent School District (Box 88)
  - Vandiver, Ann M. (Box 88)
  - Vance, Rep. & Mrs. Arthur (Box 88)
  - Vance, Carol S. (Box 88)
  - Vastine, Mr. Boone (Box 88)
  - Vaughn, Casey (Box 88)
  - Vaughn, Mrs. Marilyn (Box 88)
  - Vaughn, Pete (Box 88)
  - Vaughn, Lt. William T. (Box 88)
  - Vaught, Mrs. W. E. (Box 88)
  - Vazquez, Roger A. (Box 88)
  - Vehicle Registration (Box 88)
  - Vela, Manuel G. (Box 88)
  - Vending Association (Box 88)
  - Verdi, Ms. Esther (Box 88)
  - Veterans Affairs Commission (Box 88)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars Auxiliary (Box 88)
  - Via, Mrs. Duann (Box 88)
  - Vice, Mrs. Jessie L. (Box 88)
  - Vietnam (Box 88)
  - Villalobus, Joe (Box 88)
  - Virgin, Earl Jr. (Box 88)
  - Visiting Nurse Service (Box 88)
  - Vivian, Mr. & Mrs. Roy (Box 88)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation (Box 88)
  - Volunteer Services Council (Box 88)
  - Volunteers In Service to America (Box 88)
  - Vomastek, R. D. (Box 88)
  - Vordenbaum, Mrs. Ferne (Box 88)
  - Voter Registration (Box 88)
  - Voyles, Mrs. Ann (Box 88)
  - Voyles, Buck (Box 88)
  - Vale, Rep. Bob R. L. (Box 89)
  - Valles, State Rep. Robert (Box 89)
  - Val Verde County (Box 89)
  - Vance, Ms. Freida (Box 89)
  - Vanloh, Raymond (Box 89)
  - Vanloh, Mrs. V. H. (Box 89)
  - Van Houten, Robert E. (Box 89)
  - Van Huss, Ms. Thelma (Box 89)
  - Van Kirk, Ms. Diana (Box 89)
  - Van Loh, Ms. Harold (Box 89)
  - Van Loh, Ms. Thelma (Box 89)
  - Vannoy, Mr. Steve (Box 89)
  - Varelman, Ms. Dian (Box 89)
  - Vargas, Mrs. Wilma (Box 89)
  - Varnadore, Ms. Linda (Box 89)
  - Varnell, Mrs. Betty (Box 89)
  - Varner, Ms. Daisy (Box 89)
  - Vaughn, Mrs. H. H. (Box 89)
  - Vaughan, Kenneth (Box 89)
  - Vaughn, Ms. Mary (Box 89)
  - Vaughn, Wayne (Box 89)
  - Vaught, Ms. Lois A. (Box 89)
  - Vecchio, Jim (Box 89)
  - Vehon, Mr. & Mrs. David (Box 89)
  - Veitenheimer, Ralph (Box 89)
  - Vendrich, Ann (Box 89)
  - Vernon Regional Jr. College (Box 89)
  - Veteran's Administration (Box 89)
  - Vick, Larry (Box 89)
  - Vickers, Candace (Box 89)
  - Vickers, Stanley (Box 89)
  - Vickery, Mrs. Tom (Box 89)
  - Victor, Chris (Box 89)
  - Victoria, TX (Box 89)
  - Vieth, Ruth Ann (Box 89)
  - Villegas, Ms. Val (Box 89)
  - Vinson, G. L. Jerry (Box 89)
  - Vinson, Robert E. (Box 89)
  - V.I.S.T.A. (Box 89)
  - Vista Cablevision (Box 89)
  - Bureau of Vital Statistics (Box 89)
  - Vocational Agriculture Teachers Association of Texas (Box 89)
  - Vocational Education (Box 89)
  - Vocational Homemaking Teachers Asociation of Texas (Box 89)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation Commission (Box 89)
  - Vogel, Irvin J. (Box 89)
  - Volking, Harold (Box 89)
  - Vollers, Mr. Jim (Box 89)
  - Volunteers (Box 89)
  - Von Dohlen, Rep. Tim (Box 89)
  - Vordenbaum, Aubrey (Box 89)
  - Vowells, Raymond (Box 89)
  - Voyles, Jim (Box 89)
  - Wayford, J. H. (Box 89)
  - Wayne, Ralph (Box 89)
  - Wear, Mr. Harry (Box 89)
  - Weatherford College (Box 89)
  - Weatherford, Mr. James L. (Box 89)
  - Webb, Austin (Box 89)
  - Webb, Miss Mary (Box 89)
  - Webb, Mrs. Maxine (Box 89)
  - Weeks, Mary Frances (Box 89)
  - Weeks, Mr. Fred (Box 89)
  - Wegman, Mrs. Philip S. (Box 89)
  - Wehner, Dr. Walter L. (Box 89)
  - Weinert, Mrs. H. H. (Box 89)
  - Welborn, E. E. (Box 89)
  - Welch, Mr. & Mrs. Harold T. Jr. (Box 89)
  - Welch, Mr. & Mrs. Jack (Box 89)
  - Weldon, Joyce (Box 89)
  - Welfare File 1 (Box 89)
  - Welfare File 2 (Box 89)
  - Wade, Lee (Box 89)
  - Wallace, Tom (Box 89)
  - Wallander, Miss Carol (Box 89)
  - Washing Machine & Dryer Papers (Box 89)
  - Weedon, William (Box 89)
  - Wescott, Gordon (Box 89)
  - White, Mrs. Heyward (Box 89)
  - White, William Louis (Box 89)
  - Wichita Falls Symphony Orchestra (Box 89)
  - Williams, Bobby (Box 89)
  - Williams, Dr. & Mrs. Temple (Box 89)
  - Wilson, Mrs. Thomas (Box 89)
  - Windjammer Club (Box 89)
  - Woolard, Mr. & Mrs. Gerald (Box 89)
  - Kim Yung Ho World Vision (Box 89)
  - Worthington, George Y. III (Box 89)
  - Wright, Dr. & Mrs. William W. (Box 89)
  - Wristwatch Papers (Box 89)
  - Wright, Mr. & Mrs. Jim (Box 89)
  - Wackius, Mrs. Eula (Box 89)
  - Waco, Texas (Box 89)
  - Waco Chamber of Commerce (Box 89)
  - Waddell, A. R. (Box 89)
  - Waddle, W. F. (Box 89)
  - Wade, Billy A. (Box 89)
  - Wade, Mr. & Mrs. Lee (Box 89)
  - Wages, Mrs. C. D. (Box 89)
  - Wages, Mr. & Mrs. Jack D. (Box 89)
  - Waggoner, Dick (Box 89)
  - Waggoner, Mr. & Mrs. Merle T. (Box 89)
  - Waggoner, T. J. Jr. (Box 89)
  - Wagnon, Mr. Herbert J. (Box 89)
  - Waight, Mr. & Mrs. A. J. (Box 89)
  - Walden, H. H. (Box 89)
  - Waldrip, Dr. & Mrs. Don (Box 89)
  - Walker, Mr. Bill (Box 89)
  - Walker, Mr. Bob H. (Box 89)
  - Walker, Mrs. Elvin (Box 89)
  - Walker, E. S. B. (Box 89)
  - Walker, Rev. Jerry G. (Box 89)
  - Walker, Leona S. (Box 89)
  - Walker, Mary (Box 89)
  - Walker, Miss Nancy (Box 89)
  - Walker-Neer Manufacturing Co. (Box 89)
  - Walker, Mrs. Smitty B. (Box 89)
  - Wallace, C. W. (Box 89)
  - Wallace, Miss La Rue (Box 89)
  - Wallis, Myrtle E. (Box 89)
  - Walsh, Mrs. F. Howard (Box 89)
  - Walsh, Miss Sylvia (Box 89)
  - Walters, Dillard (Box 89)
  - Walton, Mr. Charles E. Jr. (Box 89)
  - Walton, Mrs. Corrie (Box 89)
  - Wampler, Clifton B. (Box 89)
  - Ward, Charles (Box 89)
  - Ward, Mr. & Mrs. J. Dawson (Box 89)
  - Ward, Joe (Box 89)
  - Ward, Rev. John D. (Box 89)
  - Warehousing (Box 89)
  - Warfield, Francine (Box 89)
  - Warren, Jimmy L. (Box 89)
  - Warren, Mrs. Nadine (Box 89)
  - Wassgren, William J. (Box 89)
  - Waste Disposal (Box 89)
  - Water File 1 (Box 89)
  - Water File 2 (Box 89)
  - Water Resources Institute (Box 89)
  - Water Safety (Box 89)
  - Waters, Ron (Box 89)
  - Watkins, Mrs. Eula (Box 89)
  - Watson, Mr. H. M. (Box 89)
  - Watson, Melvin W. (Box 89)
  - Watson, Murray Jr. (Box 89)
  - Watson, Robert S. (Box 89)
  - Watson, W. Marvin (Box 89)
  - Wyatt, Joe Jr. (Box 89)
  - Wachsman, Cecil L. (Box 90)
  - Waddell, Mr. & Mrs. Woodrow (Box 90)
  - Wade, Ms. Frances Lee (Box 90)
  - Wade, Juanita D. (Box 90)
  - Wade, Ms. Pam (Box 90)
  - Wade, Ms. Toni (Box 90)
  - Wages, Mrs. Jack (Box 90)
  - Wagoner, Elmer Lee (Box 90)
  - Wagoner, Glen (Box 90)
  - Waggoner, Mrs. Bob (Box 90)
  - Waggoner, Faye E. (Box 90)
  - Wagner, Bryan P. (Box 90)
  - Wakefield, Mrs. Billie (Box 90)
  - Wakeman, Jeanne (Box 90)
  - Walbourn, Charles E. (Box 90)
  - Walker, Albert G. (Box 90)
  - Walker, Chin (Box 90)
  - Walker County Historical Commission (Box 90)
  - Walker, Elsie (Box 90)
  - Walker, Eva M. (Box 90)
  - Walker, Jay (Box 90)
  - Walker, Mr. & Mrs. John (Box 90)
  - Walker, Mrs. Lista (Box 90)
  - Walker, Mrs. Mattie R. (Box 90)
  - Walker, Reese W. (Box 90)
  - Walker, Ms. Robbie J. (Box 90)
  - Wall, Mrs. Frances L. (Box 90)
  - Wall, Julie (Box 90)
  - Wall, Mary Kate (Box 90)
  - Wallace, C. W. Jr. (Box 90)
  - Wallace, Ms. Doris H. (Box 90)
  - Wallace, Jack R. (Box 90)
  - Wallace, Jim (Box 90)
  - Wallace, Mr. Luther (Box 90)
  - Wallace, Mack (Box 90)
  - Wallace, Mrs. Marjorie (Box 90)
  - Wallace, Rep. Ralph (Box 90)
  - Wallace, Mrs. S. R. (Box 90)